<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/preview/pr-10/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/preview/pr-10/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-04-25T18:11:07+00:00</updated><id>/preview/pr-10/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Pividori Lab</title><subtitle>We are a research laboratory at the University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus. We design advanced machine learning methods applied to human disease with a systems biology approach.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Initializing Pividori Lab</title><link href="/preview/pr-10/2023/04/24/initializing-pividori-lab.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Initializing Pividori Lab" /><published>2023-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-25T18:09:59+00:00</updated><id>/preview/pr-10/2023/04/24/initializing-pividori-lab</id><content type="html" xml:base="/preview/pr-10/2023/04/24/initializing-pividori-lab.html"><![CDATA[<p>On May 1st, 2023, I’ll officially start as an Assistant Professor and PI of the <a href="https://pivlab.org/">Pividori Lab</a> in the <a href="https://medschool.cuanschutz.edu/dbmi">Department of Biomedical Informatics</a>, <a href="https://medschool.cuanschutz.edu/">University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus</a>.
I won’t write a long post about this, just saying that I’m very excited about this new stage in my career.
I invite you to keep an eye on this blog, <a href="https://twitter.com/miltondp">my Twitter</a> and <a href="https://github.com/pivlab">our projects on GitHub</a> for updates about our research and other activities.</p>

<p><strong>We are recruiting!</strong> So if your interests overlap with <a href="https://pivlab.org/research/">our labs’</a>, please reach out!</p>]]></content><author><name>milton-pividori</name></author><category term="lab,research" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 1st, 2023, I’ll officially start as an Assistant Professor and PI of the Pividori Lab in the Department of Biomedical Informatics, University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus. I won’t write a long post about this, just saying that I’m very excited about this new stage in my career. I invite you to keep an eye on this blog, my Twitter and our projects on GitHub for updates about our research and other activities.]]></summary></entry></feed>