<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/preview/pr-7/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/preview/pr-7/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-04-24T19:43:02+00:00</updated><id>/preview/pr-7/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Pividori Lab</title><subtitle>We are a research laboratory at the University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus. We design advanced machine learning methods applied to human disease with a systems biology approach.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Initializing Pividori Lab</title><link href="/preview/pr-7/2023/04/24/initializing-pividori-lab.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Initializing Pividori Lab" /><published>2023-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-24T19:42:11+00:00</updated><id>/preview/pr-7/2023/04/24/initializing-pividori-lab</id><content type="html" xml:base="/preview/pr-7/2023/04/24/initializing-pividori-lab.html"><![CDATA[<p>Officially, today I start as an Assistant Professor and PI of <a href="https://pivlab.org/">Pividori Lab</a> in the <a href="https://medschool.cuanschutz.edu/dbmi">Department of Biomedical Informatics</a>, <a href="https://medschool.cuanschutz.edu/">University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus</a>.
I won’t write a long post about my feelings, but I’m very excited about this new stage in my career.
I invite you to keep an eye on this blog, <a href="https://twitter.com/miltondp">my Twitter</a> and our <a href="https://github.com/pivlab">GitHub repos</a> for updates about our research and other activities.
We are recruiting, so if your interests overlap with <a href="https://pivlab.org/preview/pr-7/research/">our labs’</a>, please reach out!</p>]]></content><author><name>milton-pividori</name></author><category term="lab,research" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Officially, today I start as an Assistant Professor and PI of Pividori Lab in the Department of Biomedical Informatics, University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus. I won’t write a long post about my feelings, but I’m very excited about this new stage in my career. I invite you to keep an eye on this blog, my Twitter and our GitHub repos for updates about our research and other activities. We are recruiting, so if your interests overlap with our labs’, please reach out!]]></summary></entry></feed>